jackpotcitycasino.com 2016-12-19

# JackpotCity Online Casino – Casino Terms

## General

Bayton Limited is committed to protecting and respecting Your privacy. Bayton Limited complies with all applicable data protection and privacy laws. If You do not understand how we handle or use the personal information You provide to us then You are invited to send in any questions to [support@thepalacegroup.com](mailto:support@thepalacegroup.com). 

## Information Collected

Telephone calls may be recorded or monitored for training and/or security purposes. By using this service, you are consenting to the recording or monitoring thereof Bayton Limited may collect and record all internet communications, details of transactions you carry through the site and details of your visits to the site.

## Processing of Personal Details

Any personal data received in regards to a Player and/or registrant is:  

  * processed in accordance with the rights of the Player concerned
  * obtained only for a specific and lawful purpose
  * kept in a secure manner
  * is utilised for marketing purposes based on the opt–out principle.

## Storage and use of Personal Data

During the registration process and when you subsequently use your Casino account, specific Personal Data ("Personal Data") is collected including, but not limited to, first and last name, date of birth, credit card Data, home or other physical address, email address, phone number or other contact Data. All of your Data is collected and stored in a secure and protected environment and is correct as it is provided. You are entitled by law to have a copy of the Personal Data recorded and to have any Personal Data corrected. You may change your personal details at anytime by sending us an email [support@thepalacegroup.com](mailto:support@thepalacegroup.com). 

Disclosure of your Personal Data will only take place in accordance with applicable laws. Such disclosure will primarily be to other Bayton Limited companies, business partners and marketing affiliates, service providers, consultants or suppliers that are engaged to carry out financial or other processing on our behalf. 

Due to the nature of the internet, its use to collect and transfer Personal Data it may necessitate the transmission of your Personal Data outside of the EEA. By using this site you acknowledge and agree to our use of your Personal Data in this manner. We do not collect your Personal Data when you use our Site without your knowledge or rent, sell or trade your Personal Data to any third party. 

Your Personal Data may be disclosed for processing to any of the following persons or entities: (i) any companies within our group and their employees who have a need to know such information; (ii) our business partners and affiliates (collectively: " **Marketing Affiliates** ") for different marketing purposes (see below under "Player Relationship Management (CRM) and Marketing Materials") (iii) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of our companies; (iv) any payment processors who assist us in receiving and making payments to and from you; and (v) our licensing authority. 

Any processing performed by any of the aforementioned persons or entities will, if required by law, be governed by an agreement protecting your Personal Data. If we sell all or part of our business, sell or transfer some or all of assets, are involved in a merger, acquisition or business transfer, or in the event of bankruptcy, we may disclose and transfer your personally identifying information to a purchaser, acquiring party or other third party involved in the transaction. 

In such an event, you will be notified via email or notice posted on our website explaining your options regarding your personal information and the identity of the new data processor responsible for handling your personal information. 

You may ‘opt out’ of receiving any promotional communications either by choosing to opt out where such option is made available on the Site or in an email you receive from us, or at any time by sending an email [support@thepalacegroup.com](mailto:support@thepalacegroup.com). 

## Fraud Prevention

To protect us and any other users of the Site against fraud including use of stolen credit cards, or any other fraudulent or criminal activity (including any chargeback or other reversal of a payment) we may check your details against, and share Personal Data with other online gaming sites, banks, credit card companies and other fraud prevention agencies. In addition, money laundering legislation requires all financial institutions to collect and record Personal Data to confirm a customer’s identity and to report any transactions arousing suspicion. 

## Player Relationship Management (CRM) and Marketing Materials

Bayton Limited reserves the right to process personal data for CRM purposes.  
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If You follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before You submit any personal data to these websites. 

We also share and disclose Personal Data, such as your name, email address, telephone number, etc. with our Marketing Affiliates for the purpose of providing You different marketing offers we or our Marketing Affiliates believe are relevant for You. Our Marketing Affiliates may use this Personal Data for different marketing techniques, such as direct email, SMS and telephone marketing purposes. 

Out of respect to your right to privacy we provide You within such marketing materials with means to decline receiving further marketing offers from us. At any time, You may request to unsubscribe and discontinue receiving marketing offers by contacting us at [support@thepalacegroup.com](mailto:support@thepalacegroup.com). 

If You unsubscribe we will remove your email address from our marketing distribution lists and from any future lists we may share with our Marketing Affiliates. However, You may need to separately unsubscribe from marketing offers sent by our Marketing Affiliates. Please note that even if You unsubscribe from our marketing mailing list, we may continue to send You service–related updates and notifications. 

**You hereby acknowledge and agree that by downloading, installing or accessing our Services, we may share your Personal Data with our trusted partners and Marketing Affiliates for the purpose of direct marketing.**

## Security of Processing

Your security as a customer is of the utmost importance to us. Online security measures such as passwords and account numbers are used when all transactions take place to ensure that no one can gain access to your financial or personal details. When you open an account at the Casino, your details are fully encrypted by the strictest 128–bit SSL encryption for total security. When Personal Data is transferred over the Internet, we and our e–commerce partner use 128–Bit Secure Socket Layer Encryption Technology to ensure the security of all Personal Data. All commercial transactions at the Online Casino are facilitated by Datacash Ltd, the internet's premier e–cash merchant. They provide our Customers with safe and secure e–cash and play an active role in fraud prevention and detection. Their aim is to ensure the integrity of client’s accounts and safeguard payments made to you. Risk sentinel, advanced fraud–management software that protects the Online Casino customers from online fraud, has been implemented to provide you with ongoing protection. 

## International Transfer

As we operate internationally, it may be necessary to transfer your Personal Data to other companies within our group or to parties with whom we have contracted for certain services to assist us in delivering our services to you. These parties may be located in countries outside the European Union. The data protection and other laws of these countries may not be as comprehensive as those in the European Union. If you choose to provide us with Personal Data, you expressly consent to us transferring that information to, and storing it on, servers located outside of the European Union – in these instances we will transfer and store your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. 

## Your consent

By clicking "I agree" during the registration process or by your continued use of the Site following the posting of this Privacy Policy (as applicable), you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy and will notify you of these changes by posting the modified terms on our online site. 

## Correction of Incorrect Account Information

You have the right to require access to Your own personal data and/or have the right to correct and/or erase wrong and/or inappropriate data. 

## Cookies / ActiveX

Bayton Limited Website works by using cookies and Active X components for (but is not limited to) the following purposes: 

  * To identify the Player's preferred language so it is automatically selected when the Player returns to Bayton Limited
  * To store information about the Player's preference's and so to allow us to customise our site according to the Player's individual interests
  * For analysis of Bayton Limited Website traffic so as to allow us to make suitable improvements
  * The operation of the games (such as the flash casino)
  * To serve advertisements which Bayton Limited believes will be of interest to You

Please be aware that it may not possible to use the Website or Services without accepting these components. If additional information is required, please email [support@thepalacegroup.com](mailto:support@thepalacegroup.com). 

## Legal Disclaimer

Please also visit our rules, terms and conditions covering the use and limitations of liability governing the use of the Online Casino web site and software.

## Other linked websites

Where there is a link from this website to another relevant site, this privacy policy will not apply once you leave this site.

## Right to use the Software

You are permitted to install and use the Software and all content derived from the Software in connection with the use of the websites in accordance with these Terms & Conditions. The Software allows You to use our gambling services available via the websites (the 'Services'). You may install the Software on a hard disk or other storage device and may make backup copies of the Software, provided that such backup copies are used only by You in connection with the Services through a computer of which You are the principal user. The Software's code, structure and organization are protected by intellectual property rights. You must not:

  * copy, redistribute, publish, reverse engineer, decompile, disassemble, modify, translate or make any attempt to access the source code to create derivate works of the source code, or otherwise 
  * sell, assign, sublicense, transfer, distribute or lease the Software
  * make the Software available to any third party through a computer network or otherwise
  * export the Software to any country (whether by physical or electronic means)
  * use the Software in a manner prohibited by applicable laws or regulations

You will be solely liable for any damage, costs or expenses arising out of or in connection with the commission of any Non–Permitted Usess.

Back to Top
